Guide to the John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955,
Comstock, John Henry and Anna Botsford papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955, 1874-1931 (bulk)
21-23-25
Anna Botsford, Comstock 1854-1930.
6.7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, engravings, watercolors, photographs, slides, published materials, clippings, and notes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes personal correspondence of Anna Botsford and Henry John professional correspondence; publications by or about the Comstocks; lecture and field notes; certificates and awards; typescript draft of an autobiography by Anna Comstock, published posthumously as The Comstocks of Cornell: John Henry Comstock and Anna Botsford Comstock; Botsford and Comstock family photographs; Anna Botsford diaries and poem; a scrapbook relating to the Botsford family, Phebe Irish Botsford, and Anna Botsford Comstock; materials concerning wood engraving; photographs and sketches (pen and ink and pencil).
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
John Henry Comstock was a professor of entomology at Cornell University. Anna Botsford Comstock was a professor of nature studies and a wood engraver specializing in scientific illustration.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes personal correspondence of Anna Botsford and Henry John (later John Henry) Comstock, 1859-1923; professional correspondence (1878-1926) documenting John Henry Comstock's influence in the development of entomology departments in colleges throughout the United States; publications by or about the Comstocks; lecture and field notes; certificates and awards; typescript draft of an autobiography by Anna Comstock, published posthumously as THE COMSTOCKS OF CORNELL: JOHN HENRY AND ANNA BOTSFORD COMSTOCK edited by Glenn W. Herrick and Ruby Green Smith, 1953; Botsford and Comstock family photographs; Anna Botsford diaries (1870-71, 1874-75) and poem; a scrapbook relating to the Botsford family, Phebe Irish Botsford, and Anna Botsford Comstock; materials concerning wood engraving; photographs and sketches (pen and ink and pencil) of insects by Anna Comstock used in Comstock Press publications; glass lantern slides used in Anna Comstock's nature study classes; wood block; engraving tools; and wood engravings of plants, insects, and nature scenes by Anna Botsford Comstock.
NATURE SONGS AND STORIES, by Katherine Creighton, illustrated by Anna Comstock, Comstock Publishing Company, 1914, autographed by Creighton and Comstock.
Woodcuts and drawings by others, presented to the Comstocks.
Bound manuscript "Jottings - Spiders," probably written by John Henry Comstock for Jennie Bartlett. Also, samples of various printing and engraving techniques, probably collected by Anna Botsford Comstock.
Photocopy of typescript letter from Henry Comstock to Charles Darwin regarding Comstock's report on cotton insects (June 4, 1880).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1854-1930.; Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1854-1930.; Comstock, John Henry, 1849-1931.; Comstock family.; Botsford family.; Botsford, Phebe Irish.; Botsford family; Botsford, Phebe Irish; Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1854-1930; Comstock family; Comstock, John Henry, 1849-1931; Comstock, John Henry, 1849-1931.; Creighton, Katherine.; Herrick, Glenn W. (Glenn Washington), 1870-1965.; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Cornell University
Subjects:
Biological illustration.; Entomology -- Study and teaching.; Insects.; Nature study.; Scientific illustration.; Zoology.; College teachers.; Entomologists.; Naturalists.; Women artists.; Women naturalists.; Biological illustration; College teachers; Entomologists; Entomology -- Study and teaching; Insects; Naturalists; Nature study; Scientific illustration; Universities and colleges -- Faculty; Women artists; Women naturalists; Zoology
Form and Genre Terms:
Autobiographies.; Drawings.; Genealogies.; Lantern slides.; Lecture notes.; Diaries -- 19th century. -- United States; Photographs.; Poems -- 19th century. -- United States; Syllabi.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. John Henry Comstock certificates and newspaper clippings
Series III. Anna Botsford Comstock materials
Series IV. Lecture and field notes
Series V. Anna Botsford Comstock autobiography
Series VI. Printed material
Series VII. Botsford and Comstock family photographs
Series VIII. Wood engravings, sketches, drawings, and photographs by Anna Botsford Comstock
Series IX. Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence
  - Anna Botsford and Henry John (later John Henry) Comstock personal correspondence
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1859-1864 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1866 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1867-1868 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1871 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1873 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1876-03-13-1882-12-31 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1884-02-17-1885-03-29 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1885-04-05-1885-09-27 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1887-02-20-1907-11-23 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1914-1926 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Herrick, Glenn Washington, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Comstock, Anna Botsford, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Comstock, John Henry, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
  - John Henry Comstock professional correspondence
    Correspondence is physically arranged chronologically in the boxes but has been arranged alphabetically and then chronologically in this guide for easier search.
    - A-F
      - Aaron, S. Frank, 1889-06-11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Aaron, S. Frank, 1889-06-27 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Abbott, Lyman, 1891-07-14 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Abeir, William M., 1887-07-19 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Abeir, William M., 1894-07-09 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Academy of Natural Sciences, 1889-12-16 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Adams Express Co., 1889-12-16 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Adams Express Co., 1890-03-05 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Adams Express Co., 1891-01-07 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1821-11-01 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1885-10-13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1885-12-19 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1886-05-08 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1887-11-03 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1888-03-19 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1888-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1889-04-22 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1890-04-17 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1890-05-09 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1891-02-04 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1891-05-28 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Adams, Charles Kendall, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Adams, Cyrus Cornelius, 1891-05-11 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Adams, Cyrus Cornelius, 1892-06-18 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Adams, Henry Carter, 1886-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Adams, Mrs. Charles Kendall, 1891-05-03 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Adams, Mrs. Charles Kendall, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Adsitt, Carrie Ingersoll, 1893-06-14 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Adsitt, Mary, 1891-02-20 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        W.O. Wyckoff, Remington Typewriters
      - Agassiz, Alexander, 1892-12-29 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Akhurst, John to Williams, E.S., 1887-07-05 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        Regarding pins
      - Akhurst, John to Williams, E.S., 1890-02-15 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Akhurst, John to Williams, E.S., Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Albro, S.H., 1898-01-05 (Box 6, Folder 17)
        Principal, State Normal School
        Mansfield, Pennsylvania
      - Aldrich, Irwin Dayton, 1892-11-02 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Aldrich, Irwin Dayton, 1894-08-30 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Aldrich, John Merton, 1889-07-13 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Aldrich, John Merton, 1892-11-21 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Aldrich, John Merton, 1894-01-07 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Aldrich, John Merton, 1894-03-16 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Aldrich, John Merton, 1900-04-12 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Allen, D.C., 1891-02-06 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Allen, George H., 1890-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Allen, Ida, 1889-07-29 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Allen, Ida, 1889-08-13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Allen, John J., 1886-07-13 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Uncle, Baptist minister
      - Allen, John J., 1886-10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Allen, John J., 1887-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Allen, John J., 1888-03-16 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Allen, John J., 1888-06 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Allen, John J., 1890-06-02 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Allen, John J., 1891-03-12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Allen, John J., 1899-06-18 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Allen, John J., 1900-03-23 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Allen, Mary S., 1885-07-23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Allen, R.W., 1892-05-26 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Alvord, Henry Elijah, 1885-06-03 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Alvord, Henry Elijah, 1885-07-28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Alvord, Henry Elijah, 1891-01-24 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Alvord, Henry Elijah, 1892-12-31 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Alwood, William B., 1886-09-14 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Alwood, William B., 1887-03-16 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Alwood, William B., 1887-03-31 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Alwood, William B., 1891-04-04 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Alwood, William B., 1891-05-14 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Alwood, William B., 1891-09-17 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Alwood, William B., 1891-10-06 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Alwood, William B., 1894-07-14 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Alwood, William B., 1894-07-23 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Amadeo, Antonio T., 1886-04-27 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Amadeo, Antonio T., 1887-04-23 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Amadeo, Antonio T., 1888-03-05 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1884 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1885-12 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1889-12-14 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1890-08 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1884 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        receipts
      - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1885 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Ames, Charles Wilberforce, 1890-04-01 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Ames, Charles Wilberforce, 1890-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Ames, Charles Wilberforce, 1891-10-14 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Anderson, Charles Henry, 1885-09-22 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Anderson, Charles Henry, 1886-08-11 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Anderson, Charles Henry, 1888-03-19 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Anderson, Charles Henry, 1890-04-19 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Anderson, Charles Henry, 1890-12-04 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Anderson, Charles Henry, 1891-01-24 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Anderson, Henry C.L., 1891-11-02 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        Department of Agriculture
        Sydney, Australia,
      - Andrew, John, 1896-04-21 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Andrews, A.C., 1899-03-21 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Andrews, I.C., 1890-07-16 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Andrews, I.C., 1891-03-01 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Andrews, Mary Hunt, 1897-02-09 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Andrus and Church, 1885-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Andrus and Church, 1886-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Andrus and Church, 1887-05-12 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Andrus and Church, 1887-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Andrus and Church, 1888-02-13 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Andrus and Church, 1888-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Andrus and Church, 1888-07-12 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Andrus and Church, 1889-04-16 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Andrus and Church, 1889-05-01 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Andrus and Church, 1889-05-22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Andrus and Church, 1889-11-26 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Andrus and Church, 1890-01-13 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Andrus and Church, 1890-10-27 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Andrus and Church, 1890-11-15 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Andrus and Church, 1891-01-14 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Andrus and Church, 1891-01-31 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Andrus and Church, 1892-06-08 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Andrus and Church, 1892-06-11 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Andrus and Church, 1892-12-20 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Andrus and Church, 1893-07-17 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Andrus and Church, 1894-01-02 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Andrus and Church, 1894-02-15 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Angell, G.W., 1893-12-23 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Angle, Clarence B., 1893-12-01 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Anthony, E. and H.T., 1888-05-15 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Anthony, E. and H.T., 1888-06-09 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Anthony, E. and H.T., 1888-06-25 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Anthony, E. and H.T., Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Appleton and Co., 1889-12-21 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Appleton and Co., 1892-06-16 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Appleton and Co., 1892-06-18 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Appleton and Co., 1892-08-23 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Arnold, George B., 1889-04-26 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Arnold, W.H., 1896-12-20 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Arthur, Joseph Charles, 1885-07-13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Arthur, Joseph Charles, 1889-01-09 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Arthur, Joseph Charles, 1889-03-07 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Arthur, Joseph Charles, 1889-07-30 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Ashmead, William H., 1881-10-24 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Athletic Council of Cornell, 1887-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Atkinson, E.I., 1888-02-10 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Atkinson, E.I., 1888-05-03 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Atkinson, E.I., 1888-05-18 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Atkinson, E.I., 1888-12-29 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1885-09-15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1885-10-02 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1885-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1885-11-02 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1885-11-23 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1885-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1886-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1886-05-31 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1886-10-19 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1887-04-11 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1887-06-28 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1887-07-06 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1887-07-14 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1887-11-11 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1888-03-09 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1888-03-24 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1888-04-09 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1888-05-03 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1888-05-16 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1888-07-17 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1888-10-11 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1890-01-22 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1890-02-06 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1890-04-22 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1892-08-17 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, 1892-08-27 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Atkinson, George Francis, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Atlantic Monthly, 1889-07-03 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Atlantic Monthly, 1889-07-19 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Atlantic Monthly, 1889-07-26 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Atlantic Monthly, 1889-09-25 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Atlas Tack Corp, 1891-06-20 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Atwater, Fred, 1890-12-15 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Aust, Peter, 1897-12-02 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Austin, Ben W., 1887-02-27 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Austin, Blanche Tudor, 1900-04-05 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Bachelor, Ida, 1885-06-02 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Bachelor, Ida, 1901-01-14 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Bachelor, Ida, 1901-01-25 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Bailey, Banks and Biddle Co., 1894-06-15 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Bailey, Liberty Hyde, 1889-09-25 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Bailey, Liberty Hyde, 1889-11-01 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Baimlhet, Louise, 1892-01-26 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Baimlhet, Louise, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Baird, Raymond, 1888-10-05 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Baker Brothers and Co., 1888-02-24 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Baker, Carl F., 1894-10-27 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Baker, Carl F., 1894-11-08 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Balch, W.J., 1891-05-21 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Ball, Charles Hubbard, 1890-05-30 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Banks, Nathan, 1889-04-19 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Banks, Nathan, 1891-04-17 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Banks, Nathan, 1892-04-06 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Banks, Nathan, 1892-06-16 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Barber and Lieberson, 1889-05 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Barber, A.D., 1887-07-19 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Barber, A.D., 1890-04-10 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Barber, A.D., 1890-05-03 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Barber, A.D., 1890-06-18 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Barber, A.D., 1890-06-28 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Barber, A.D., 1890-07-23 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Barber, A.D., 1891-05-24 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Barber, A.D., 1894-05-07 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Barney, William Grant, 1888-05-12 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Barrett, Charles G., 1893-08-22 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Barry, Patrick, 1887-01-25 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Barry, Patrick, 1888-12-06 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Barry, Patrick, 1888-12-08 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Barry, Patrick, 1889-12-05 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Barry, W.C., 1890-12-26 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Bartholomew, F.S., 1887-09-30 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Bartlett, J.C., 1890-02-23 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Bartlett, J.C., 1890-03-05 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Bartlett, J.C., 1890-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Bartlett, J.C., 1890-09-20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Bartlett, J.C., 1891-02-19 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Bartlett, J.C., 1891-03-07 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Bartlett, J.C., 1891-09-17 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Bartlett, J.C. from A.B.C., 1890-02-27 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Barto, Lucy Murray (Barto, Mrs. Daniel Otis), 1892-09-27 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Bass, Rev. William C., 1890-12-03 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Battin, John Wilson, 1890-10-10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Battin, John Wilson, 1890-10-24 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Battin, John Wilson, 1890-11-28 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Battin, John Wilson, 1891-02-04 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Battin, John Wilson, 1891-10-31 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Bauer, J.C., 1888-03-20 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Bauer, J.C., 1889-12-11 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Bauer, J.C., 1890-06-09 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Bauer, J.C., 1891-12-09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Bauer, J.C., 1892-04-28 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Bauer, J.C., 1893-05-18 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Bauer, J.C., 1893-10-07 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1888-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1888-05-22 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1888-06-25 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1888-06-28 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1888-08-09 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-06-21 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-06-24 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-08-30 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-09-28 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-10-10 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-10-14 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-10-22 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-10-23 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-12-04 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1889-12-23 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1890-06-28 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1890-10-15 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1890-10-31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1890-11-04 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1890-11-11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1890-12-02 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1894-02-12 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1894-05-05 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1894-07-24 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1894-08-01 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1894-08-30 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1896-06-14 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Bausch and Lomb Co., 1901-06-04 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Beach, Alice M., 1893-09-14 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Beach, E.F., 1900-10-13 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Beach, E.F., 1900-11-26 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Beach, E.F., 1900-12-27 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Beach, Sarah A., 1892-10-26 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Beach, Wooster, 1889-04-16 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Beach, Wooster, 1891-09-07 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Beadle, E.S., 1886-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Beal, William James, 1882-04-24 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Bean, C.M. and W.L., 1885-04-13 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        Maple Sugar, Honey, etc firm
        McGrawville, New York
      - Bean, C.M. and W.L., 1887-02-16 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Bean, C.M. and W.L., 1887-04-30 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Bean, C.M. and W.L., 1890-04-22 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Bean, C.M. and W.L., 1891-03-13 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Bean, C.M. and W.L., 1891-05-20 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Bean, C.M. and W.L., 1894-03-14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Beardsley, George F., 1893-04-05 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Beardsley, George F., 1894-04-23 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Becker, E.S., 1886-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Beckwith, M.H., 1888-09-18 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Beckwith, M.H., 1889-01-25 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Beckwith, M.H., 1889-07-27 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Beckwith, M.H., 1890-12-06 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Beckwith, M.H., 1890-12-19 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Beckwith, M.H., 1891-12-26 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Behringer, George Frederick, 1891-12-08 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Bell, W.J., 1892-08-25 (Box 5, Folder 11)
        Publisher's Weekly
      - Beltramini de Cafati, Dr. Francesco, 1885-07-19 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Benci, D., 1890-05-13 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Benedict, L.C., 1889-01-18 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Benoit, A.V., 1889-01-26 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Benoit, A.V., 1889-06-26 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Benoit, A.V., 1889-11-25 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Benton, George Alden, 1891-12-17 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Benton, W.G., 1892-03-08 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Berg, C., 1893-01-09 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Berley, Antoin, 1900-11-18 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Berwick, Edward, 1892-02-18 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Berwick, Edward, 1892-02-28 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Berwick, Edward, 1892-06-03 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Berwick, Edward, 1892-06-19 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Berwick, Edward, 1894-03-21 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Bessey, Charles Edwin, 1889-01-09 (Box 3, Folder 6)